PATRICIA PARKER

https://www.linkedin.com/in/patriciakayparker/ LinkedIn Profile https://github.com/pkpatricia GitHub Repo

https://patriciaparker.co Personal Site

Skills Summary

Developer that is knowledgeable and experienced in Web Design, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Java, Spring Boot, Android, Ruby on Rails, Python and its SciPy libraries of NumPy, Pandas, and matplotlib, SQL, Excel, Tableau, Shopify, WordPress, and Drupal.

Experience

Trilogy Educational Services

Teaching Assistant and Tutor / Sept 2018 – July 2019

Teaching Assistant and Tutor at Southern Methodist University through Trilogy Education in:

- Data Visualization,
- Python and its SciPy libraries of NumPy, Pandas, and matplotlib,
- SQL,
- JavaScript

Conjuncture Design

Web Developer Freelancer / April 2016 - present

- Design and Code Responsive E-Mails with testing done in Litmus.
- E-mails sent using MailChimp and/or Campaign Monitor.
- Create websites.

Collabera

Data Entry Associate / Dec 2014 – July 2015

 Inputted and transposed technician repair notes form Diebold systems to Bank of America systems.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Lawrence Technological University in Southfield, MI